ShinY
深影
本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址http://shinybbs.vip
■
ShinY
深影
■
ShinY
深影
■
翻译：  栗栗子 凌大 Cinnamon 凌大 螺丝鬼
强大的力量
With great power
■
校对：  负零     压制： 青鸟
带来绝对的确定性
comes the absolute certainty
你王八蛋的一面将无法隐藏
that you'll turn into a right cunt.
一切尽在我们掌控
We got everything under control.
曼哈顿发生了爆炸
An explosion rocked Midtown Manhattan.
士兵男孩
Soldier Boy.
ShinY
深影
你找到他时会怎么做
And what you gonna do when you find him?
■
你需要我们
You need us.
你注射了沃特一种未经测试的药物
You shot up an untested drug from Vought.
妮娜
Nina.
我们的机密实验室被毁了
Our classified lab destroyed...
我的超能力没了
My powers are gone!
ShinY
深影
我的三位联系人消失了
... three of my contacts disappeared,
你得为此负责
so you're the one who pays the debt.
ShinY
深影
黑人的命也是命
Black lives matter!
超人类的命也是命 忘恩负义的东西
Supe lives matter, fucking ingrates!
住手
Stop!
内森再也无法走路了
Nathan will never walk away.
他妈的搞什么 - 绯红伯爵夫人
- What the fuck? - Crimson Countess.
你的情人在来的路上
Your lover boy's on his way here.
俄罗斯人给了你多少钱
How much did the Russians pay you?
- 没给 - 我爱过你
- They didn't. - I loved you.
我恨你 我们都恨你
I hated you. We all did.
你在和一个杀人犯合作
You're teaming up with a murderer.
求你了 别去
Please don't go.
过去这几天让我有些...
Past few days have got me feeling a little, um...
看开了
well, philosophical.
超级恶棍的攻击已经影响到每一个人
Uh, these Supervillain attacks, they've affected everyone.
不管你是谁 不管你来自哪里
Doesn't matter who you are, where you're from.
没人可以幸免
We're all in this together.
但只要携手 我们就能设想一个更美好的世界
And together, we can imagine a better world.
深海
Deep.
讲真 没有其他人能操作这玩意了吗
Is there anyone else that can operate this thing? Seriously.
艾希莉认为我们该解雇他们中大部分人
Ashley thought we should get rid of most of them.
什么 是你炒掉他们的
What? You fired them.
在这 我找到了
Here, I found it. I found it.
好
Okay.
停
Stop.
放大
Zoom in.
士兵男孩
Soldier Boy.
不 这不可能 他大概
No, that's impossible. He died, like,
- 四十年前就死了 - 难道有人角色扮演
- 40 years ago. - Someone's cosplaying?
看他的脸 就是他
Look at his face. It's him.
- 或许是电脑特效 - 不是特效
- Or maybe CGI. - It is not CGI.
你甚至不知道电脑特效是什么
You don't even know what CGI stands for.
就是去你妈的
It stands for "Blow me."
我不明白 他这些年去了哪里
I don't understand. Where has he been?
他为什么杀绯红伯爵夫人
Why did he kill Crimson Countess?
他俩不是神仙眷侣吗
I mean, the two were, like, fucking
好吧 你知道吗
Kurt and Goldie. All right, you know what?
没关系 我们掌控着新闻界
This is fine. This is fine. We dominate the news cycle.
我给黑伯曼打电话 发消息说我们已经
I will call Haberman. We'll message that we got
完全控制了士兵男孩
Soldier Boy totally under control.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你想要告诉全世界 士兵男孩
You want to tell the world that Soldier Boy,
这个英雄中的英雄
hero of heroes,
死而复生
is back from the fucking dead
还炸了曼哈顿吗
and blowing up Midtown?
在我之前 他就是沃特的化身
Before me, he was Vought.
他的雕像就立在这座大楼前 艾希莉
His statue's in front of the fucking building, Ashley.
我的老天
Oh, my God,
如果这消息泄露出去
if this gets out...
公司完蛋了 我也完蛋了
company's fucked. I'm fucked.
天呐 如果公司倒了 我也完了
Oh, God. If the company falls, I fall.
该死
Oh, fuck.
老天 为什么这种事会发生在我身上
Oh, God. Why is this happening to me?
这不公平
This isn't fair.
太他妈的不公平了
This is so fucking unfair.
好吧
Okay.
这事我来解决
I'll handle this.
我会找到他并杀了他
I'm gonna find him and kill him.
你把所有录像毁了
You bury it. All of it.
不能让任何人看到
The footage, no one sees it.
如果他搞砸了 你等着遭殃
He fucks it up, it's your head.
玄色
Noir.
为什么他要杀绯红伯爵夫人
Why would he kill Crimson Countess?
他曾是你的队长 你知道原因吗
He was your team leader, you have any idea?
朋友 我真的很高兴有你和我一起面对
I'm really glad to have you with me on this one, pal.
说真的 你是我唯一可以依靠的人
Seriously. You're the only one I can count on.
谢谢
Uh... thank you.
搞什么
What the hell?
芝士烤东方酱在哪
Where's the Chop Socky Oriental Sauce?
他们没有那个酱了
They don't have that anymore.
为什么他妈的没了
Why the fuck not?
很多很多好的理由吧
Uh, many... many good reasons.
那你买到其它东西了吗
Did you get the other shit?
给 大哥
Here you go, guv.
我想死氨基丙苯了
Man, I missed bennies.
我们就是靠它登录诺曼底的
It's how we won D-Day, you know.
我们当时都磕嗨了
We were wired to the fucking gills.
听着 我们来聊聊
Listen, let's have a little chat
合作的事吧 怎样
about this team-up, yeah?
为什么我需要和人合作
Yeah, what the hell do I need a team for?
上一个和我合作的人把我出卖给了苏联
The last one handed me to the Reds.
而我们带你脱离了那个困境
And we got you out of that little pickle.
我们把绯红伯爵夫人包起来
We wrapped up Crimson Countess
跟圣诞火鸡一样送给你
and delivered her like a fucking Christmas turkey,
我甚至还帮你解决了火药
and I even sorted Gunpowder for you.
我该觉得这很了不起吗
Why am I supposed to be impressed with that?
这跟杀死伊曼纽尔·刘易斯一样容易
That's like killing Emmanuel Lewis.
好吧 他比你上次见他长大了一点
Yeah, well, he grew up a bit since you last saw him.
别他妈碰那盾牌
Hands off the fucking shield.
- 嗯 - 不管怎么说
- Mm. - Anyway,
你想要复仇小队血债血偿 对吗
you want payback on Payback, don't you?
而我们
Well, it just so happens
正好
that we
是消灭恶棍超人类的专家
are experts at exterminating shitbag Supes.
你看 如今的世界已经大不相同了
You see, it's a whole different world out there now, son.
我们可以帮你适应
We're here to help you find your way.
我自己就能找到他们
Well, I can find them on my own.
你确定?
Uh, are you sure?
我想说 你知道什么是GPS吗
I mean, do you know what a GPS is?
蓝牙呢
Or... or Bluetooth? Or, I mean...
网络呢
... the internet?
你自己编造了这些词
You made those words up.
不 这些都是真实存在的词
No. No. No, those are real words, um,
你需要这些东西来找到他们
and... and you need those to find them.
好吗 你需要我们
All right? You need us.
这小子说得对
Kid's right.
而我们要的
And all we ask in return
仅仅是在你的复仇名单上多加个名字
is that you add one more name to the list.
谁
Who?
一个王八蛋 叫祖国人
A right cunt named Homelander.
我见过照片
I've seen pictures.
他什么来历
Who is he?
他就是全新的你
He's the new you.
伙计 没人能取代我
No one's the new me, pal.
但为什么是他
But why him?
简单说 你不是唯一一个想报仇的人
Let's just say you're not the only one wants payback.
行吧
All right.
你们帮我找到我剩余的队员
You help me find the rest of my team,
我帮你们处理这个祖国人
and I'll help you with this Homelander.
你在生我气吗 因为
对不起 不会再有下次了
我们改天一起看雨中曲吧
所以你认为士兵男孩
So, you think that Soldier Boy
在追击复仇小队的其它成员
is going after the rest of Payback?
光靠伯爵夫人自己 没法干翻他
Countess wasn't strong enough to fuck him over on her own.
有人帮她
She had help.
士兵男孩才刚刚开始
Soldier Boy's just getting started.
你知道他们其他人在哪吗
Do you know where any of them are?
炸药双子太狡猾了
Those shady-ass TNT Twins
我查到一个佛蒙特州的地址
got an address in Vermont.
- 布彻知道吗 - 不知道 但他会查到的
- Okay. Does Butcher have it? - No, but he'll get it.
我认为子弹对士兵男孩没用
I think Soldier Boy is bulletproof.
这不是为士兵男孩准备的
This ain't for Soldier Boy.
听着 我也对那些人恨之入骨
Look, I'm pissed at those guys, too,
但我们需要保持头脑清醒
but we have to keep our heads on.
凭什么 凭什么总要求我高尚
Why? Why do I always have to take the high road?
你们这些白人生气时
You know, when white folks get mad,
就可以暴跳如雷
y'all motherfuckers go berserk,
凭什么我就得转过脸去?
but I got to turn the other cheek?
去他妈的高尚 去他妈的布彻 去他妈的休伊
Fuck the high road, fuck Butcher, and fuck Hughie.
休伊现在有点迷失了
Hughie is not himself right now.
休伊是个成年人 是他自己做出的选择
Hughie is a grown-ass man that's made his own choices.
马文
M.M.!
拜托 士兵男孩会杀更多人 该死的
Please. Soldier Boy is gonna kill more people. I mean, fuck.
山崎纪现在还在医院
Kimiko is in the hospital.
没有了超能力
She lost her powers.
弗兰基联系不上 阿莱克斯死了
Frenchie isn't answering, Alex is dead,
梅芙...
and Maeve...
现在只剩我们俩
We're all we've got.
全都靠我们了
It's up to us.
妈的
Shit.
我是星光
This is Starlight.
艾希莉 好的 当然 我马上到
Yeah, of course, Ashley. I'll be right there.
我得回趟总部
I got to go up to the Tower for a little bit.
现在?
Now?
如果我不去 他们会觉得不对劲的
If I don't go, they're gonna know something's up.
我一小时后回来
I'll be one hour.
我需要担心你吗
Do I need to worry about you?
好吧
Okay.
即使是最茂盛的树
Even the greatest trees
也是从一颗种子长起
must grow from a single seed.
跟随一位引以为傲的黑人 火车头
Follow one proud Black man's journey to the root of his roots,
去非洲寻根
as he takes the A-Train to Africa.
去他妈的
Jesus fucking Christ.
嗨
Hey.
这也太棒了
It looks great.
你尊严的力量展现无遗
Man, there's so much strength in dignity.
你到底要怎么处置蓝鹰
What are you doing about Blue Hawk?
好吧 首先 沃特每个人
Okay, first of all, everyone at Vought
都为你哥哥的悲剧感到痛心
is just heartbroken over your brother's tragic accident.
那不是事故
It wasn't an accident.
蓝鹰无缘无故地发疯
Blue Hawk went apeshit for no reason.
他说了他感觉受到了威胁
Well, he said he felt threatened.
- 威胁? - 嗯嗯
- Threatened? - Mm-hmm.
谁威胁他 一屋子没有超能力
By what, a room full of Black people
的黑人吗
with no superpowers?
听着 我已经安排了一个十二周的
Look, I've scheduled him for 12 weeks
敏感性训练
of sensitivity training.
去你的吧 我要的是起诉
Fuck that. I want charges brought.
火车头 对蓝鹰提起诉讼
Okay, A-Train, persecuting Blue Hawk
只会让事情更糟
will only make things worse.
现在需要的是疗愈
This is a time for healing.
我才不管呢
I don't give a shit.
我以为我们身边已经没有纳粹了
I thought we got rid of the Nazis around here.
沃特拒绝种族主义
Vought rejects racism
- 也同样抵制法西斯  - 嗯
- and Nazism unequivocally. Okay? - Hmm.
我们能不能晚点再说这个
Now, uh, can we talk about this later?
我今天事儿真的特别多 谢谢
I have a lot going on today. Thank you.
随便吧 我不需要你
You know, whatever. I don't need you.
我刚定位了他的芯片 我自己去找他
I'll just ping his chip, go get his ass myself.
别 祖国人希望所有人
No. Homelander wants everyone to present
团结一致
a united front right now.
我哥瘫痪了
My brother is paralyzed.
我现在只需要正义
I want some fucking justice.
说真的吗 正义
Seriously? Justice?
- 是的 - 你需要正义
- Yeah. - You want justice?
是
Yeah.
哦 老天
Oh, fuck.
我开了一百多个小时的
I have spent over 100 hours
危机管理会议
in crisis management meetings
就是为了解决你们的烂摊子
specifically figuring out how to cover up your bullshit...
包括你三次赤裸裸的谋杀
including all three of your straight-up murders...
当时你要么跟你的伙伴在夜店
while you were out in the club with your crew,
要么是在跟刺爪女乱搞
or getting your toe sucked by Popclaw,
别忘了 你也是杀人犯
who, let's not forget, you also murdered.
是的 我知道
Yeah, that's right. I know about that.
你不在乎
You did not give a shit
自己造成的连带损失
about all the collateral you caused then.
现在你突然在乎起来
Now, all of a sudden, you care
就因为你切身体验了
because it happened to you?
去你的吧
Go fuck yourself.
是的 我说了
Yeah, that's right.
我说出来了
I said that.
大声说出来了
Out loud.
祖国人
Homelander.
- 怎么了 - 几件事
- What? - Couple things. Uh...
玄色 他离开了
Noir, he's, uh, he's gone.
你说他离开了 是什么意思
What do you mean, he's gone?
他把自己的追踪芯片挖了出来
He cut out his tracking chip.
不 他...
No, he... he... he...
他不会的 不会是玄色 他不会跑的
He... he wouldn't. Not Noir. He wouldn't run.
额
Well...
他不会这么对我
He wouldn't do that to me.
他不会跑
He w... he wouldn't run.
告诉他我们发现了什么
Tell him... what we figured out.
好的
Right.
我们认为绯红伯爵夫人只是开始
We think Crimson Countess was just the start.
我们认为 他是冲着
We think... he's going after
整个团队来的 包括玄色
his whole team, including Noir.
好消息是 这也意味着我们知道
The good news is, that means we know
他下一步会针对谁
where he's probably headed next.
炸药双子
The twins. TNT.
他们是最亲密的 佛蒙特州
They're the closest. Vermont.
好的
Okay.
好 真的吗 祖国人 我太感谢你了
Okay? Really? Homelander, thank you so much.
你去佛蒙特州
You go there,
你找找看
and you check it out.
- 好的 - 如果士兵男孩真的出现了
- Yeah. - And if Soldier Boy does show up,
然后 额
then, uh...
- 你联系我 - 好的
- you call me. - Yeah.
- 我跟双胞胎怎么说 - 我才不在乎
- what should I tell the twins? - I don't give a fuck.
明白了
Got it.
宝贝 这可太棒了
Babe, that was amazing.
但你知道吗 我不需要你跳进来
Yeah, but, you know, I didn't need you to jump in there
我自己能掌控全局
like that. I had the whole thing.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.
我只是想帮忙
I'm just trying to help. Okay?
我们共同推进这件事
We're in this together, right?
行 好的
Okay. Right.
好耶
Right.
为什么耷拉着脸 老虎
Why the long face, tiger?
如果我搞不定他怎么办
What if I can't handle him?
我是说 如果玄色离开
I mean, if Noir ran...
你能搞定他
Oh, you can handle him.
你站在食物链的顶端
You're the top of the food chain.
嘿 嘿
Hey, hey.
我们小时候
When we were kids,
独自被关禁闭
alone in the bad room,
我都让我们挺了过来 对吧
I got us through it, right?
总是如此
Don't I always?
- 总是如此 - 无论发生什么
- Always. - No matter what.
无论发生什么
No matter what.
而现在 我也会让我们挺过去的
And now, I'll get us through this.
只要你和我在一起
Just as long as you and me stick together.
但是 如果埃德加是对的呢
But... what if Edgar's right?
如果征服沃特是个错误呢
What if it was a mistake to take over Vought?
而且 而且
And... and...
我只是徒有其表 他们都知道我是个骗子
and I am just talent, and they all know I'm a fraud.
你为什么要在乎一堆烂人的想法
What do you care what a bunch of mud people think?
来吧
Come on.
告诉我真正的原因 我想听你说
Tell me the real reason. I want to hear you say it.
- 说出来 - 我希望他们爱我
- Say it! - I want them to love me.
太对了
Yahtzee!
就这一件事从来都没有实现 对吧
Only it never seems to work out, does it?
马德琳 梅芙 风暴女
Madelyn, Maeve, Stormfront,
甚至你亲儿子
even your own son.
那你为什么接着撞向同一堵南墙
So why do you keep running headfirst into the same brick wall?
我不知道
I don't know.
自欺欺人 你心知肚明
Pants on fire. You know.
这是因为 内心深处
It's because, deep down,
你还是有一个部分
there's a part of you that is still...
是人类
human.
- 不是 - 部分是
- No. - Mm-hmm. Part of you is.
肮脏 枯萎
- Mm-mm. - A dirty, shriveled,
干涸的那部分
anemic little part of you
啜泣哭求认可和爱
that still mewls for approval, and love,
我要妈妈 我要爸爸 呜呜呜呜
and a mommy, and a daddy, and a boo-hoo-hoo.
看着我 老虎
Look at me, tiger.
看着我
Look at me.
你得把人类的部分像切除癌症一样切除掉
We got to cut that part of you out like a cancer.
然后
And then, well,
然后 我的孩子 你就终于可以
then, my boy, you can finally be
成为你应该成为的样子
who you were always meant to be.
纯洁 干净
Pure. Clean.
大理石一般
Like marble.
这些人宁可去死 也不要当苏联的奴隶
These people would rather die than be Soviet slaves.
太晚了
It's too late.
阿富汗是我们的了
Afghanistan is ours.
错 它是自由的
Wrong. It's free.
我会跟圣战兄弟们站在一起直到最后
And I'll stand by our mujahideen brothers until the end.
你知道我还会做什么吗
You know what else I'll do?
什么
What?
让你分心
I'll distract you.
炸药双子 引爆
TNT! Detonate!
该死的双胞胎
These fucking twins.
你知道他们没办法正中目标
You know they couldn't hit their fucking marks?
他们就是业余的
Fucking unprofessionals is what they are.
布彻会找到他们的
Hey, uh, yeah, Butcher's gonna find them.
不然你去睡会儿
Why don't you, uh, why don't you get some sleep?
不用 我睡够了
Mm, no. I've slept enough.
各位爸爸 我们知道
Dads. We know
你喜欢带着你们的孩子到处走
you love taking your babies everywhere.
无论你去哪儿 星光婴儿纸尿裤
No matter where you go, Starlight Diapers...
男人们真的这样走来走去吗
Do men really walk around like that?
我是说 爸爸会
Yeah. I mean, dads do.
行吧
Okay, well...
比尔·考斯比是美国国民爸爸
Bill Cosby is America's dad, and,
再告诉你一件事
tell you one thing, he
他宁死也不会用那种娘炮用品
wouldn't be caught dead in that pussy gear.
好多事还没告诉你
Lots to unpack there. Uh...
考斯比 那可是真男人
The Cos. That's a real man.
老天爷
Holy shit,
他会调很多烈酒
did he make some strong drinks.
我的老天爷
Holy fucking shit.
不过 讲真 如今怎么才算是真男人
But, seriously, what passes as a man today?
我的主啊
Christ on a cross.
我读到咱们跟阿富汗干起来了
I read that we were ass up in Afghanistan.
怎么回事  阿富汗人挺好的啊
The fuck is up with that? Those were the good guys.
我是说 我离开的时候 还是...
- I mean, when I left, it was, uh... - Yeah, you know...
我是说 老天爷 我们节节胜利
I mean, goddamn it. We... we were ten and one, you know?
我带着116步兵团登陆奥马哈海滩
I lead the 116th onto Omaha Beach.
我深入鹰巢
I was in the fucking Eagle's Nest.
为了这个国家而战
I fought for this country.
我曾为这个国家而战
我得到什么了
And what did I get for it?
被遗忘
Forgotten.
被自己人扔下 自生自灭
Left to rot by my own team.
我当时想跟伯爵夫人
You know, I wanted some rug rats of my own,
要小孩儿
with Countess. Yeah.
那个臭婊子
Ain't that a bitch.
生他几个小子 抚养他们长大
You know, couple of little boys. Raise them up
成为真男人
to be men.
现在
Now...
现在我一无所有
... now I got nothing.
我能问你个问题吗
Hey, um, can I ask you something?
曼哈顿发生了什么
What happened in Midtown?
我不知道
I don't know.
我是说 你的队伍不在那儿
I mean, your team wasn't there,
是不是有人说了什么 或者做了什么
so did someone do anything, or say something...
- 我说了我不知道 - 好 好
- I said I don't know. - Okay. Okay, yeah.
我晕过去了
I blacked out.
大概十分钟
About ten minutes.
当我清醒过来时 悲剧已经酿成
When I came to, the damage was done.
我没有想伤害那些人
I didn't mean to hurt those people.
我并不是个坏人
I'm not a bad guy.
但这种事不会再发生了...
But that won't happen again...
是吗
right?
除非他们再来招惹我
Only if they got it coming.
你在流血
You're bleeding.
不是我的 搞到一个地址
Not mine. Got an address.
我们要去佛蒙特了
We're off to Vermont.
七海之王
Lord of the Seven Seas. Wow.
老天 我可是铁粉
My man, I'm such an incredible fan.
天呐 汤米 你跪舔的样子真恶心
Jesus, Tommy. Slather his balls in peanut butter, why don't you?
抱歉 我妹妹是个臭婊子
Sorry. My sister's a goddamn bitch.
炸药双子
And, uh, TNT.
我也是你们的铁粉
Right. I'm a big fan of yours, too.
穿搭很棒
Cool outfits.
话说 我一直星光那件事
Always felt you got railroaded
影响了你的前途
with that Starlight thing, by the way.
什么世道
You know, like, what,
如今你都不能赞美一位女士
nowadays, you can't even pay a lady a compliment.
- 可不是吗 - 你真恶心
- I know, right? - You're disgusting.
总之 我们非常高兴
Anyway, we are just so pleased, you know,
能够有你这样一位大明星
have a big star such as yourself
莅临我们的小小派对
grace our humble soiree.
你们在举办派对吗
You guys having a party?
等等 这是...
Wait, is this... ?
这是超英高潮趴
This is Herogasm.
你能来我很高兴
I'm really glad you're here.
我很想你
I missed you.
- 还有谁会来 - 他们没告诉你吗
- Who's joining us? - They didn't tell you?
各位好呀
Hey, there.
你好 女士
Hey, lady.
市长想说什么都行
The mayor can say anything she wants,
但一直在努力追捕这家伙的
but Homelander is the one working
- 可是祖国人 - 嗯哼
- to catch the guy. - Mm.
我们现在到了一个转折点
We're about to turn a corner here.
确实如此
Absolutely, we are.
- 谢谢 亲爱的 - 应该的 甜心
- Thank you, honey. - Of course, sweetheart.
这真让人安心
That's reassuring.
但现在又有十九人死亡 几十人受伤
But there are 19 dead and dozens wounded.
纽曼议员
Congresswoman Neuman,
你想对电视机前担惊受怕的美国观众们
what do you say to the Americans who are watching right now
- 说些什么吗 - 听着 可以理解...
- and feeling scared? - Yeah, look, it's understandable...
这是个... 什么烂问题
What kind of a... a nasty question is that?
不 没关系 我很乐意回答...
Oh, no, it's fine. I'm happy to answer...
星光刚刚说了 我也一直在说
Starlight just said, and I keep saying,
根本没有问题
this is not a problem.
抱歉 先生 我不是那个意思...
I'm sorry, sir, I didn't mean...
我没时间理会你这些平庸的舆论围攻
I don't have time for your mediocre ambush.
你的工作是报道事实
Your job is to report facts,
而不是当我们告诉你真相时 你还要抨击我们
not attack us when we sit here and tell you the truth.
美国人民 他们明白
The American people, they know.
他们知道什么时候有人在讲述真相
They know when someone's telling them facts,
也知道什么时候媒体在欺骗他们
and they know when the media is lying to them.
根本没有问题
There is no problem.
出门是安全的 完毕
It is safe to go out. Period.
你知道吗 我们到此为止了
You know what? We're done here.
该死的蠢货
Stupid fucking hack.
接下来 查克会和瑞秋·雷一起做肉馅饼
Up next, Chuck makes empanadas with Rachel Ray.
我们马上回来
We'll be right back.
切出了
And we're clear.
你个该死的三脚猫 下次报道
You fucking amateur. The next report
你就在我的屁眼里面做吧
you're gonna be doing is inside my fucking asshole,
你个该死的蠢货
you piece of shit.
你有时间聊聊吗
Hey, uh, you free for a little catch-up?
我现在有点忙
You know what? I'm... I'm a little slammed right now.
拜托 十分钟不会要你的命的
Oh, come on. Ten minutes won't kill you.
休伊在哪
Hey, so, uh, where's Hughie?
他和他父亲去露营了
Oh, he's just camping with his dad for a couple of days.
好 挺好的
Okay. Okay, good.
好极了 我以为他在躲着我
Oh, great. I thought he was avoiding me
- 什么的 - 不 不
- or something, you know... - No, no.
... 因为害怕我会爆掉他的头
... 'cause he was scared I was gonna pop his head.
什么
Hmm?
拜托 安妮
Come on, Annie.
收起你的超能力
Put them away.
我不会伤害你
I'm not gonna hurt you
也不会伤害休伊或你的家人
or Hughie or your families.
而且 你打不过我
Besides, you'd lose.
那你为什么来
Then why are you here?
因为我想帮你
Because I want to help you.
帮我
Huh. Help.
炸掉了国会的疯子居然这么说
From the psycho who blew up Congress.
听着 众议院里的大多数人都在转发
Look, most of those guys passed around deepfakes of me
我为本·拉登吹箫的换脸照片
on the House floor blowing bin Laden,
所以我完全不同情他们
so I'm not exactly overwhelmed with sympathy.
安妮 你需要我
Annie, you need me.
你现在孤身一人
You're all alone.
拜托 那个祖国之光的超话
I mean, come on, that "Hashtag Homelight" Shit?
把你拍的像个人质似的
That looks like you're in a hostage video.
如果我错了 你就眨眨眼
Blink twice if I'm wrong.
而且 你还得对在你第一天上班时
And, what, you got to play nice with the guy
逼你为他口交的家伙笑脸相迎
that throat-fucked you on your first day of work.
还有梅芙 他们说梅芙在康复中心
And Maeve, they say Maeve is in rehab,
但你我都知道她可能已经死了
but you and I both know she's probably dead.
我是你唯一的依靠了
I'm all you got.
来嘛 安妮 我们是朋友
Come on, Annie, you and I were friends.
对我来说这一点从未改变
None of that has changed for me.
你打算兜圈子到什么时候
Are you ever gonna get to the point?
你有一亿九千三百万粉丝
You have 193 million Instagram followers.
让我借用你的影响力 我也把我的借给你
Lend me your influence, and I'll lend you mine.
我可以保护你不受祖国人的伤害
I can protect you from Homelander.
你最后会成为真正的队长
You'll finally be team captain for real.
反过来 你可以帮我增加支持率
And in return, you help me goose my numbers.
我就可以通过我的教育改革议案了
I can finally get my education reform bill passed.
我们可以让一切变得更好 安妮
We can make things better, Annie.
为了我的女儿
For my daughter,
为了很多人的女儿
for a lot of daughters.
拜托 你觉得怎么样
Come on, what do you say?
你说得对
You're right.
这整个地方
This whole place.
我真的受够了...
I'm so fucking tired...
... 听人告诉我
... of listening to people tell me
要赢 必须不择手段
I need to be shitty in order to win.
去你的
Fuck you.
去他妈的祖国人 去他妈的沃特
And fuck Homelander, and fuck Vought
和不择手段的屁话
and this "Whatever it takes" Crap.
你最终只会坐上
You're just gonna end up
你一手造成的
sitting on top of the steaming pile of shit
烂摊子上
that you built.
我受够了
I'm done.
我他妈受够了 我不干了
I'm fucking done. I'm not doing it anymore.
如果祖国人杀了你
You're not gonna be doing anything
你就什么都做不了了
if Homelander kills you.
也许是
Yeah, maybe.
但我会知道我没有助纣为虐
But then I'll know I'm not working with a fucking nutjob.
所以 要不爆掉我的头
So, either pop my head
要不就滚出去
or get the hell out.
以下这些话不要说出去
Hey, keep this between us?
干掉美国甜心是很难
It'd be really tough to take out America's sweetheart,
但不是不可能
but not impossible.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
不
No.
不 不 别这么做
No, no. Don't do this.
他的身体是一件艺术品 不是吗
His body is a masterpiece, no?
你知道这个伤痕的故事吗
Do you know the story behind this one?
几年前 我的表妹科雅去美国作证
Oh, years ago, my cousin Kolya went State's witness, so
我派去了我的塞尔盖
I send my Sergei.
三发子弹都挡不住我的猛犬
Not even three bullets could stop my attack dog.
巴斯克海岸上的酒吧争斗
Bar fight on the Basque coast.
是他挑起来的
He started it.
我的野兽 这是我最喜欢的
Oh, my beast. This is my favorite.
塞尔盖十四岁时打碎了一个玻璃杯
When Sergei was 14 years old, he dropped a glass.
他父亲让他跪在玻璃渣上
His father told him to kneel in the shards
直到他同意才能动
and not move until he said so.
小塞尔盖纹丝不动
Little Sergei did not shift an inch,
甚至到他父亲离开 去喝得大醉
not even after his father left to get drunk
在妓院里昏过去都没动过
and pass out in the whorehouse.
拜托 别为了塞尔盖哭
Oh, please, don't cry for Sergei.
他喜欢别人告诉他做什么
He likes to be told what to do.
他也喜欢做错事时被惩罚
And he loves to be punished when he's bad.
这让他更坚强
Makes him hard.
不
No.
那么... 雪莉...
So... Cherie...
- 不 - ...还是山崎
- No. - ... or Kimiko?
不 不要
No, don't do it.
不要 妮娜
Don't do this! Nina!
你必须选择 塞尔盖
You must choose, Sergei.
如果不选 我就会
If not, I will kill
把她俩都杀了 等你尖叫痛哭完后
both of them, and when you've finished
我会把你也杀了
screaming, crying, I will kill you, too.
- 快选 - 不
- Choose. - No.
该死
Fuck.
不
No.
山崎 快跑
Kimiko, run!
山崎
Kimiko!
不
No!
该死 该死 该死
Oh, fuck! Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
她走了
She's gone.
妮娜走了
Nina's gone.
结束了
It's over.
你一直都有这个习惯吗
Have you always had that?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我在哈林区长大
I grew up in Harlem,
和一家人挤在褐砂石房子里
brownstone filled with family.
祖父母 叔叔阿姨和表兄妹们
Grandparents, uncles, aunts, cousins.
一天晚上
One night,
外面发生了骚动
there was a ruckus outside.
我从窗户看出去 是士兵男孩
I looked out the window, and it was Soldier Boy.
他抓了几个想偷奔驰的小孩
He had pulled up on some kids that were trying
所以我跑过去叫醒了我爷爷
to boost a Benz, and so I run and wake up my granddad.
爷爷 爷爷 是士兵男孩 快来看
"Grandpa, Grandpa. It's Soldier Boy. Come look."
士兵男孩举起奔驰
Soldier Boy takes the Benz,
向我们的房子抡过来
and he hurls it through our house,
就像货运火车
like a fucking freight train.
离我就差六英寸 我侥幸逃过
It missed me by about six inches.
但我爷爷
And my grandpa...
上一分钟他还在那儿
One minute he was there...
下一分钟就没了
... and then he wasn't.
是我叫醒了他
And I woke him up.
导致他站在那个地方
I put him in that spot.
那不是你的错
That is not your fault.
强迫症就是那个时候开始的
That's when this whole OCD shit started.
我不明白为什么
I mean, I don't understand it.
我只知道如果我一晚上
All I know is that if I didn't check the burners
不检查三次灶台
three times a night,
士兵男孩就会回来 杀掉我们所有人
Soldier Boy would come back and kill the rest of us.
而我还是那个
And I'm still that kid.
会半夜醒过来
Still getting up in the middle of the night,
检查灶台的孩子
checking the burners.
因为如果我不检查
'Cause if I don't,
士兵男孩就会回来
Soldier Boy's gonna come back,
杀了我全家
and he's gonna kill my family.
我必须要让这个狗娘养的离开我的脑子
I got to get this motherfucker out of my head,
终结于此
and end this.
否则我就被终结了
Or it'll end me.
- 我的天 - 哦 该死的
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. - Oh, hell nah.
- 我的天 - 有邀请函吗
- Oh, my God. - Invitation?
邀请函在这儿 给你
I got your invitation right here.
嘿
Hey.
星光 我刚没认出你来
Starlight. I did not even recognize you.
请进 欢迎你来参加派对
Come in. You are more than welcome to party.
- 派对 - 是啊
- Party? - Yeah.
超英高潮趴七十周年纪念
The 70th anniversary of Herogasm.
- 我去 - 哎哟
- Fuck me. - Oh.
- 哦 该死的 - 去他的
- Oh, shit. - Fuck.
你看着眼熟
You seem familiar.
你要是不把这该死的
You about to get familiar with these hands
爱之香肠 从我脸上拿开
if you don't get this motherfucking love sausage
我就把它掰断
away from my goddamn face.
- 好的 - 你不是超人类
- Okay, okay, okay. - You are not Supe.
我跟她一起的
I'm with her.
参加派对
For the fuck party.
其实 他口活儿了得
Yeah. Um, mm-hmm. No, he's very good at cunnilingus.
- 嗯 他的舌头... - 哦 怎么样
- Yeah, his tongue is just... Yeah. - Oh, yeah?
他能对着阴道狼吞虎咽
He just gobbles that vagina right up.
吧唧 吧唧 吧唧 吧唧
Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom, nom.
- 是的 - 爱之香肠 哟
- Mm-hmm. - Love Sausage, huh?
给我取了个好名字
This is good name for me.
我喜欢 进来吧
I like it. Come on in.
哦 我的老天爷
Oh, my God.
我去
Oh...
也就是说 每年一次 一群三流超级英雄
All right, so once a year, a bunch of C-listers
在其中一人的住处
get together at one of their places
一起为爱鼓掌
to get they wicks wet.
停
Stop.
- 超英高潮趴 - 嗯
- Herogasm. - Mm-hmm.
- 懂了 - 千年杀啊
- I get it. - Holy ass-ramming.
恶心
Ew.
停
Aw, stop!
快来 舔我
Come on. Come on my hump.
就是这儿
That's it.
可怜的弗兰基
Poor Frenchie.
他一直想见识这种场面 他肯定会心碎的
He's always wanted to see this. He's gonna be heartbroken.
- 你知道最不好的是什么 - 是什么
- You know what's fucked up? - Hmm?
这儿有真正的性工作者
It's that it's real fucking sex workers here
被干得死去活来 痛不欲生
getting banged up, and not in the good way.
但这些超人类毫不在乎
Not that these Supes give a shit.
士兵男孩来到这里
When Soldier Boy gets here,
肯定大开杀戒
it's gonna be a slaughter.
我们得让这些人赶紧离开这里
We have to get these people out.
你好 兄弟
What up, bro?
那个傻叉在我夹克上
What the fuck did this motherfucker
- 蹭上了什么 - 哦 老天爷
- put on my jacket? - Oh, my God. Okay. Um...
这是我最喜欢的夹克
It's my favorite fucking jacket.
- 咱们找个卫生间 - 太他妈恶心了
- Let's go find a bathroom. - Some nasty-ass shit.
- 咱们找个卫生间 - 黏糊糊的
- Let's go find a bathroom. - This shit is sticky.
去清理一下 走吧
Let's go clean it up. Let's go.
- 这他妈是什么玩意 - 黄尾刺身
- What the fuck is this shit? - Yellowtail sashimi?
不要 没心情 谢谢
No. No, not in the mood for that. Thanks.
- 天杀的  - 喷射啦
- Goddamn it. - Throwing ropes.
哦 糟了
Oh, shit.
舔吧 美味小熊熊
Lick it up, you yummy brown bear.
我受不了了
I can't.
我需要卫生间
I need a bathroom.
立刻 马上
Right now.
行吧 所以说 这就真的是个淫乱派对
Oh, okay. So, this... this is an actual orgy.
就是字面意思
That's what this is.
神他妈的超英高潮趴
Fucking Herogasm.
够牛逼
Still a thing, eh?
我干的 我在1952年创办的
It's my thing. I founded it in '52.
我和另一个超人类 自由女神
Me and this other Supe, Liberty.
兄弟 她可是真骚
Man, was she a firecracker.
弗兰基错过这个可要心碎了
Frenchie's gonna be heartbroken he missed this.
里面的人属实不少
There are a lot of people in there.
只要他们不挡我的道 就不会有事
Well, as long as they stay out of my way, they'll be fine.
好的 给我三分钟
Okay, all right. Just, uh, give me three minutes.
我迅速进去 迅速出来
I'll jump in, I'll jump back out.
我会告诉你双胞胎的准确位置
I'll tell you exactly where to find the twins.
没有人会挡你的道
Nobody else in your way.
三分钟
Three minutes.
士兵男孩 不可能 他死翘翘了
Soldier Boy? Nah, he's dead as dog shit.
不 他没死
No, he's not.
我发誓这是真的
I swear, this is really happening.
求你了 你得帮我让这些人离开这儿
Please, you need to help me get people out of here, now.
星光 别这样
Starlight, come on.
别让恐惧
Do not let them do this to you.
影响你
This... this fear.
你听到祖国人怎么说了
You heard what Homelander said.
那些自媒体就会小题大做
Lamestream media's making a fucking mountain out of a molehill.
- 自己查吧 - 哦 我的天
- Do the research. - Oh, my God.
这是真的
This is real.
发生的攻击都是真的
These attacks are real.
士兵男孩是真的
Soldier Boy is real.
我只是觉得
Well, I just think you
别什么都信
could stand to be a little better informed.
祖国人会处理好一切 好吧
Homelander's gonna take care of it, okay?
我要去搞菊花了
I'm gonna go find a salad to toss.
不好意思
Excuse me.
你把我的阴茎环熔化了
You melted my cock ring.
老天 你伸得好长
Oh, Jesus, your stretching powers!
我的天 你的嘴可真厉害
Oh, my God, your mouth is amazing.
就像天鹅绒吸尘器 吸干我的蛋蛋
It's like a velvet vacuum draining my balls.
你真火辣
Oh, yeah. You are so fucking hot.
老天 腿不要停 好爽
God, your legs go on for days.
我的老天
Ooh. Ooh. Oh, my God.
- 你在干什么 - 我去
- What the fuck? - Shit.
不是你想象的那样
It's not what it looks like.
你在做什么
What are you doing here?
没什么 我什么也没做 你怎么会在这儿
Nothing. I'm not doing anything. Why would you even...
这只章鱼生病了 你为什么问这个
This octopus was sick. Why would you ask that?
- 祖国人可要喜欢死了 - 别 等等
- Homelander is gonna love this. - No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait.
求你了 别照 别
Please, please, please. Stop. Stop, stop, stop. No.
行 听着
Okay. Okay, okay, okay. Look.
祖国人让我来的 这是他的主意
That's why I'm here. It's his idea.
什么主意
What's his idea?
我说了厕所不能照相 汤米
I said no cameras in the toilets, Tommy.
- 相机还我 - 你真可悲
- Give it back. - You're pathetic.
你知道么
You know what?
咱们走着瞧 看大家怎么想
Let's see how everyone feels about close-ups
未经允许拍摄他们菊花的行为
of their assholes without consent!
去的你 我不玩了
Fuck you. I'm done.
我永远不想再见到你
I never want to see you again.
你真好
Oh. That's so sweet.
只是 我得让菊花休息一会儿
Uh, just, I got to give my asshole a breather.
那你就跟下周波基普西市的
Then say goodbye to that Westfield mall opening
西地商城开幕式说拜拜吧
next week in Poughkeepsie, 'cause nobody
因为没有我 没人想看你
is coming to see you without me.
我恨你 恨你这张嘴
I fucking hate you. I hate your mouth.
我恨你每次嚼东西时下颌骨响
I hate the way your jaw pops when you chew.
我恨抓住你湿乎乎手
And I hated every second I spent
的每一秒
holding that clammy hand.
我真应该在子宫里就杀了你
I should've killed you in the womb.
啊 去死吧
Ah, fuck you!
你去死
Fuck you!
去你的吧 汤米
Fuck you, Tommy!
不好意思
Sorry.
我知道你喜欢日超人类
Hey, I know you like fucking Supes,
但不能日我
but I'm off the table.
我不是为这个来的
That's not why I'm here, okay?
况且你也在这儿
You're here, too, you know.
随你便 小色鬼
Whatever, Pornhub.
现在没时间跟你纠缠
I don't have time for you right now.
嘿
Hey.
你从来没道歉
You never said you were sorry.
什么
What?
罗宾的事儿
For Robin.
你从来没有因为罗宾而道歉
You never apologized for Robin.
老天爷 此时此地你要追究这个
Jesus, you want to do this right now?
对 没错
Yeah, I do.
你就是能逍遥法外 对吗
You just get away with everything, don't you?
对被你伤害的人不屑一顾
Just running past all the broken people you leave behind.
好吧 听着
All right, you know what?
什么
What?
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这是你想听的对吗
Is that what you want to hear?
因为我真的抱歉
'Cause I am.
行了吧
Okay?
确实很惨
It's fucked up,
眼见自己的爱人受到那样的伤害
seeing somebody that you love get hurt like that.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
真的很抱歉 休伊
I'm fucking sorry, Hughie.
- 休伊 休伊 - 你怎么能这样
- Hughie. Hughie. - How did you do that?
- 停 - 不 不 你怎么可以这样
- Stop, stop! - No. No, no, no. How the fuck did you do that?
- 我再做一次给你看 - 不
- I'll show you again! - No.
绝对不行
That is not going to happen.
火车头 离开这里
A-Train, get out of here.
你活该挨打
Not that you deserve the warning.
过来
Come on. Come on.
到这边来
Come on, come on.
他在这里吗
Is he here?
他只是为了双胞胎 好吗
He's only here for the twins, all right?
其他人不会受伤
Nobody else has to get hurt.
你无权决定别人的生死
You don't get to decide who to serve up on a platter here, okay?
他们都是活生生的人 我们要马上清场
These are real people. We need to clear the house now.
这里马上就要变成血池地狱了
This is about to be a fucking bloodbath.
不 不会的 我让士兵男孩保证不搞事...
No, it won't. I made Soldier Boy promise not to do anything...
休伊 别说了 听我说
Hughie, stop it. Listen to me.
祖国人马上来了
Homelander is coming.
深海告诉我的
The Deep told me.
他们打起来的时候...
When those two start fighting...
拜托了 帮帮我
Please. Help me.
- 你得走了 - 不 我要阻止他
- You have to go. - No. I need to stop him.
安妮 不 安妮
Annie. No, Annie.
安妮
Annie!
天啊... 你传送了我
Oh, my God... You teleported me?
什么鬼
What the fuck?
我救了你 安妮
I saved you, Annie.
天啊 我只是想救你
Jesus Christ. All I want is to save you.
你天天说这些 但我不需要你救我
You keep saying that, but I don't need you to save me.
好吧 上帝禁止我救你
Right, God forbid I help you,
因为我一直是那个弱者
because I always have to be the weak one,
- 需要你来拯救的那个 - 不
- the one you have to rescue. - No.
你一直是那个强者
You always have to be the strong one.
你一直比我强很多
You always have to be so much stronger than me.
我以为你不在乎
I thought that you didn't care about that.
我是说 我们第一次约会时
I mean, on our first date,
你说了这没关系
you said that it didn't bother you.
我知道
I know.
但是我在乎
But it does.
有时候
Sometimes.
一点点
A little.
我以为药物毁了你 休伊 但是...
I thought the drugs had fucked you up, Hughie, but...
... 这才是你
... this is you.
这才是真的你
This is all you.
氟烷
Halothane.
你觉得它能怎么样
What'd you think you were gonna do with that?
你杀了我家人
You killed my family.
哪一个
Which one?
嘿
Oi.
不是他
Not him.
双胞胎在外面
Twins are out there.
你可以动祖国人 但是我不能动士兵男孩
So you get Homelander, but I can't get Soldier Boy?
你是个彻头彻尾的伪君子 布彻 滚
You're a fucking hypocrite, Butcher. Now move.
我不能让你这么做 马文
I can't let you do it, M.
这是自杀
It'd be suicide.
放下它 你要干什么
Oh, come off it. What you gonna do with it?
滚
Move!
你真是个蠢货
You're such a fucking idiot.
离开我你连电视都不会用
Can't even work the TiVo without me.
搞定了 混蛋
And there it is, sick fuck.
大家好 孩子们
Hiya, kids.
这个屁眼都被干松了
That poop chute's had a workout, huh?
就像林肯隧道
Looks like the Lincoln Tunnel.
本
Ben.
你毁了我 你这个
You fucked me, you selfish
自私的狗屎
piece of shit!
够了
That's enough.
- 尼加拉瓜不是我们的错 - 我发誓
- Nicaragua wasn't our fault. - Yeah, swear to God.
那么是谁的错
Then whose fault was it?
你说出来 我可能会放你们走
If you tell me, maybe I'll let you go.
它... 是玄色 是玄色的主意
I... it was Noir. It was Noir's idea,
从头到尾
top to bottom.
他把你卖给了俄国人 拜托了
He gave you to the Russians. Please.
- 玄色 - 嗯嗯
- Noir? - Uh-huh.
- 是 - 沃特不点头
- Yeah. - Noir wouldn't take a shit
玄色屁都不敢放
without Vought's say-so.
求求了 这就是事实
Please? It's the truth.
- 把你的手给我 - 这么多年了
- Give me your hand. - It's been years.
你想死吗
Do you want to die?
引爆炸药
TNT detonate!
- 我得走了 - 安妮 等等
- I got to go. - Annie, wait.
安妮 安妮 安妮 就...
Annie, Annie, Annie, just...
你不能走
You can't go.
我不能
I can't?
我不会让你走的
I'm not gonna let you.
哦 不
Oh, shit.
不 不
No. No.
我现在不想听
I don't want to hear it right now.
蓝鹰
Blue Hawk!
- 什么 - 我们得聊聊
- What? - We got to talk.
天啊 现在不行 这里面有个神经病
Jesus Christ, not right now. There's a psycho back there.
什么鬼 把你的脏手拿开
The fuck? Get your fucking hands off me.
你伤害了很多人 你伤害了我的兄弟
You hurt a lot of people. You hurt my brother.
你逃不掉的
You're not gonna get away with it.
这次不行
Not this time.
干
Fuck!
天啊
God.
帮帮我
Help me.
救... 救救我...
S... someone please help...
解决了
Sorted?
发生了什么
What happened?
威廉·布彻和士兵男孩
William Butcher and Soldier Boy.
确实
Of course.
你们是幕后黑手
You are behind this.
这一切
This whole thing.
都是因为我
It really is all about me.
威廉 我们说好的
William, we made a deal
只有你和我一决生死
to fight to the death, you and me.
这是作弊
This is cheating.
协议取消
Deal's off.
我看着你的英雄事迹长大
You were my hero growing up.
你所有的电影我都看了几百次
I watched all your movies, hundreds of times.
你是唯一曾和我同样强的人
You were the only one that was nearly as strong as me.
兄弟 你觉得你看起来很强吗
Buddy, you think you look strong?
你穿个披风
You're wearing a cape.
你只是个廉价仿品
You're just a cheap fucking knockoff.
不 不 不
Oh, no, no, no.
我是升级款
I'm the upgrade.
马文 马文
M.M. M.M.
马文 拜托 我需要你 有人受伤
M.M., M.M., please, I need you. People are hurt.
马文 马文 拜托了
M.M.! M.M. Please.
他没有控制你
He doesn't control you.
我们得帮助这些人
We have to help these people.
选择权在我们
It's up to us.
我还以为你有多牛逼
You really had me going for a minute there.
嘿
Oi.
什么鬼
What the fuck?
你做了什么
What have you done?
毁灭吧
Scorched earth.
动手
Do it!
休伊
Hughie!
走开
Get out of here!
不可能
No fucking way.
让我看看
Let's see?
嘿
Hey.
对不起
I'm sorry.
拜托了 不 放松
Hey, please, no. Easy.
我们需要一个医生重新缝针
We need a doctor to resew these stitches.
总是我
It was always me.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我怪V把我变成了一个怪物
I blamed the V for making me a monster
但是...
but...
这不是真的
that's not true.
我就是我
It is just who I am.
不
No.
你不是怪物
You are not a monster.
看起来不论我们怎么努力逃脱
It seems no matter how much we try to run,
我们依然无法逃脱我们的命运
we cannot escape our old lives, huh?
我猜没人能逃脱命运的安排
I suppose no one can run that fast.
这些事情
Those things
小妮娜说的关于你的
Little Nina said about you
都不是真的
are NOT true.
是
Yeah.
这是个坏主意
This is a bad idea.
祖国人把我变成了美国甜心
Homelander helped make me America's sweetheart.
他会后悔的
He's gonna regret that.
- 你准备好了么 - 嗯
- You ready? - Mm-hmm.
我在蒙特皮尔 佛蒙特州
I'm in Montpelier, Vermont.
十二个英雄和平民遇难
Twelve heroes and civilians are dead,
更多的人受伤
a lot more are wounded.
现在 祖国人和沃特会告诉你
Now, Homelander and Vought are going to tell you
都怪超级恶棍 他们已经控制了局势
that it was the Supervillain and that they have it handled.
他们没有
They don't.
是士兵男孩
It was Soldier Boy.
我知道我听起来疯了 但是...
I know I sound insane, but...
士兵男孩不在乎保护美国人
Soldier Boy doesn't care about protecting Americans,
他可能从来都不在乎
and he probably never has.
大多数英雄都不在乎你们
Most heroes don't care about you.
他们只在乎自己的形象
They only care about their image, and...
祖国人是最坏的
Homelander is the worst of them.
他伤害别人
He's hurt people.
他对梅芙做了一些事情
He's done something to Maeve.
我不知道我说了实话他们会把我怎么样
I don't know what they're gonna do to me for telling the truth,
我会一直坚持下去 我本应早点站出来
but I'm going to keep doing it, and I should've done it sooner.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
还有一件事
And one more thing.
我不再是星光了
I'm not Starlight anymore.
我的名字叫安妮·詹纽艾瑞...
My name is Annie January...
... 姐退出
... and I fucking quit.
■
更多精彩 请登录深影论坛 shinybbs.vip
深影字幕组微博 weibo.com/syfansub
■
关注深影字幕组
微信公众号，更
多影视资讯，等
你来发现